reviewsforjoomla.com 2013-04-05

# Privacy Policy - Joomla Review Script, CCK, PHP Directory Script

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site or place an order.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

• To personalize your experience 

> Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.

• To improve customer service 

> Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.

• To process transactions 

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

• To send periodic emails 

> The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart and understand and save your preferences for future visits.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Public forums reminder

This site often makes forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. Exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. Although we value individual ideas and encourage free expression, we reserve the right to take necessary action to preserve the forum's integrity, such as removing any posting that is vulgar or inappropriate.

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our [Terms and Conditions](http://www.reviewsforjoomla.com/orders/terms_of_service.php) section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions about any of these practices or our use of your personal information, please feel free to contact us by web, or by mail at:

ClickFWD LLC  
CPS#7820  
P.O. Box 149020  
Coral Gables, FL 33114 

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
